Opi barua

Chattogram, Bangladesh



opibarua1122@gmail.com



+880130-0023918



linkedin.com/in/opi-barua-034524194

Summary

I am a Full Stack Developer specialized in HTML5, CSS, CSS Frameworks (Bootstrap, Tailwind, Material-UI), JavaScript, React.js, Redux, Redux-toolkit, Node.js, Express.js, Laravel, Mongoose, MongoDB, MySQL strong collaboration, problem-

solving. I have solved problems in online judges such as Outsbook.

Experience



React native development intern

Cehpoint E-Learning & Cyber security solutions Jan 2023 - Present (2 months)

Full Stack Developer

mudslide creators hub private limited Apr 2022 - Jul 2022 (4 months)

fill Full Stack Developer

Fiverr May 2019 - Apr 2022 (3 years)

Student Representative

Programming Hero Jul 2021 - Dec 2021 (6 months)

Student Representative

Creative IT Institute Sep 2019 - Feb 2020 (6 months)

Education



BGC Trust University Bangladesh

B.sc(hons) in Computer science and engineering, Mathematics and Computer Science 2019 - 2022

Skills

React Native • expo • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Responsive Web Design • Mongoose Web Server • Web Development • Data Structures • HTML5 • C (Programming Language) • Bootstrap